[tense music playing]
[breathing heavily]
- You okay. Max?
- Yeah.
[David] Alright.
- [breathing heavily]
- [radio beeps]
Ambush.
We got ambushed over here.
Vehicle's been hit.
Kröller is wounded. Shot to the shoulder.
Alright. men.
Let's get a move on! We have contact!
Send the drones up to locate the shooters.
- We're getting out now.
- Valere!
Let's move out! Now!
[suspenseful music playing]
- Here.
- Thanks.
[grunting]
[David] Alright. Almost.
On the ground. On the ground.
- [grunting]
- Here.
[drone whirring]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Cédric over radio] Eyes in the sky.
It's him. He's gonna kill me.
He's gonna take me out.
[Max] David.
Who is it?
- Who wants to kill you?
- [Kröller] Let me go and I'll tell you.
[Cédric] Drones at 300 meters.
We're approaching your position.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[gunshot]
[sniper rifle reloads]
[bullet strikes van]
[reloads rifle]
There's only one shooter.
- Cover me.
- [Max] Copy.
[David] Go.
[gunshots]
[groans]
[breathes heavily]
[Max] He's not shooting. I can't find him.
[Cédric] Drone approaching position.
[David] Let's go again.
[suspenseful music continues]
[gunshots]
[Max] I can't see him.
[David] You have a visual on the shooter?
Negative. No visual.
[Valère] Converging on target.
[gunshot]
[reloads]
We lost the drone.
- [gunshot]
- [David] Tango spotted.
Behind a big rock. Eleven o'clock.
[gunshots continue]
[gunshot]
[somber music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[Valère] We found the shooter's post.
There's a camo net and casings.
But no one's here.
Kröller's dead.
- I repeat. Kröller's dead.
- Ah. fuck.
[pants]
ELITE FORCE
[helicopter whirring]
[officers chattering indistinctly]
We widened out the search area.
but still no sign of the shooter.
What a surprise.
Did Kröller's wife say anything?
Recon's with her now but apparently
she doesn't know that much
about her own husband.
What are you thinking?
Same thing you are.
The CL-20. Christophe. now this.
The shooter was in position
when we came by.
They're not just professionals.
They know everything about us.
Yeah. And I can't say I like it.
The team recovered some ammo casings.
Maybe there's some fingerprints.
You know they're not gonna find prints.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[Rapha] It's alright.
No one's accusing you of anything.
We just want to figure out what happened.
Do you know if your father.
your husband. ma'am.
do you know if he hid anything here?
In the cottage? Or on the grounds?
[Max] Why are the kids still here?
[Valère] No one to take care of them.
Everyone's hunting for the shooter.
[Max] Their dad just died.
We can't just leave them here.
[Valère] So what?
You volunteering
after the shit you pulled?
Playing the hero can bite you in the ass.
[poignant music playing]
Here. You must be starving.
[camera shutter clicking]
[man] Right there. Another casing.
[music turns pensive]
Take the photo. I'll keep searching.
[camera shutter clicking]
Okay. good. We'll see what we get.
Okay.
Some light tracks over here.
[camera shutter clicking]
[Max] What the hell?
Stop busting my balls.
- [Valère] Who do you think you're--
- [Max] You're starting to piss me off.
I think I'm talking to you.
Just lay off me. come on!
[Valère] You're not the only one
getting pissed off. I'm not joking.
- [Max] I don't fucking care!
- [Valère] Smart-ass.
Hey! Come on. stop it!
Hey. hey. hey!
[clamoring]
Enough!
You proud of yourselves?!
Pressure's getting to you?
Well. the pressure's getting to me too!
We just got a guy killed
who was under our fucking protection!
And that's never happened to us before!
[tense music playing]
But if you're incapable of dealing with
the stress. then do us a favor and quit.
You mad? Go to the gym
and find yourself a punching bag.
Is that clear?
I said. is that clear?!
Yeah.
[music fades]
[metal tool clatters]
TECHNICAL ROOM
[device beeps]
[suspenseful music playing]
14.98.
Yeah.
[computer beeps]
MEASURING
[whirring]
[cell phone buzzing]
Yeah. Céline?
We need you here.
He's awake.
[medical devices beeping]
I knew you were gonna wake up.
Hmm.
[poignant music playing]
Don't worry. Christophe.
I'll get you some makeup.
No one'll notice a thing.
[chuckles weakly]
[Christophe groans]
Any idea who did this to you?
[exhales]
I'm gonna find them.
I promise.
[Max] It's just the three pages
so not a long read.
But if you don't mind.
I. uh… I wanna know what you think.
LAURENT VILLIERS.
LIEUTENANT KILLED IN ACTIVE DUTY
[soft jazz music playing over speakers]
Here you go.
- The chef's special. madam.
- Wow.
At the very least.
it'll fill us up before the party.
My dad's recipe.
What do you think?
What I find weird is that
the only one who was with your dad
when he died was David.
So where's his statement?
[Max] Yeah. I don't get that either.
Why wasn't it archived?
That's what I'm gonna find out.
[upbeat music playing in the distance]
- A bit basic.
- Really? Basic?
- Hey! How are you?
- Hey. what's up? Not at your internship?
- You good?
- Yeah. you?
["Sugabby" by Sad Night Dynamite
playing over speakers]
♪ Goes to Cash App
Daddy transferred her a grand ♪
♪ Life's sweet for the sugar babies… ♪
Hey!
- Thanks.
- Hi. David. it's great to see you.
- [David] Happy birthday. bro.
- You alright?
So tell me. How's he doing? You see him?
He's okay. Recovering. Slowly.
[Cédric] Hey. everyone! Excuse me!
Two seconds. okay?
Hang on! Valère.
turn the music down a bit. would you?
I won't be long.
I swear. I just wanna say two words.
- [music stops]
- To Christophe!
[all] To Christophe!
[cheering and whooping]
Now let's have some fun. alright?
[man] Yeah!
[music resumes]
Well. cheers.
[laughing]
What a fuckin' dickhead. Valère. Fuck.
Hey. I'd never say this to them
but the new guys are fire!
You're not wrong.
You alright?
I mean. at home with Jess.
Everything okay?
Yeah. It's fine. Smooth.
- Smooth.
- And she's got work.
Yeah. She's got a lot of work.
- You wanna stop doing that?
- What?
Your little negotiator tactic.
Repeating my sentences back to me
to get me to talk like I'm insane.
No way. man. At least insane guys
say something to say. you know?
Look. I know I'm drunk
but I gotta say this.
Ah. fucking hell.
You've fallen in love with me?
No. Fuck you. man. alright?
I'm being serious here.
But if you ever need to talk about Jess
or anything… Uh. I'm here. Right?
I know.
[lively dance music playing over speakers]
[laughs]
[cheering]
Yeah!
[Rapha laughing]
MISSED CALL MANON
Hey. this is Manon's voicemail.
If I didn't pick up.
it's 'cause I didn't feel like it.
Hi. it's Jess.
Leave a message after the beep.
[tense music playing]
[man] Go ahead. sir.
[David] I need a favor.
I need you to trace my daughter's number.
- [man] Yeah. No problem. sir.
- [David] Thanks.
[music fades]
- [man] It's coming from the same address.
- Thanks.
[bike engine powers down]
[techno music playing distantly]
[techno music continues over speakers]
[sniffing]
[techno music continues]
[crowd whooping and chattering]
[speaking indistinctly]
- [techno music continues]
- [people whooping]
We're leaving. Let's go!
What are you doing here?
- Hey! Hey! She's not going anywhere!
- Hey! Stop! Stop it!
- Let him go!
- Ah!
- What are you doing?
- You wanna fucking go?
You don't have to hurt them!
[yells]
- Sorry! I'm sorry!
- Move.
Out of my way.
- [Manon screams]
- [bottle shatters]
[music stops]
- [groans]
- Stop!
- [nervous chatter]
- [young man] We've gotta do something!
[grunts]
[clamoring]
[Manon] Get off of him!
- No. don't!
- [grunts]
Dad. stop it!
[taser crackles]
[Manon] Dad!
[grunting]
- Hey! Get the hell outta here!
- [women scream]
- [taser crackles]
- Let him go! Stop it! Dad!
[women clamoring]
[thuds]
[partygoers murmuring]
Let's go.
Okay. Shit.
What the hell's your problem?
[David] What's my problem?
What's your problem?
I'm obviously
missing something here. Manon.
- You sneak out. call me 15 times--
- What are you talking about?
I missed a bunch of calls from your phone!
When I call you back. you don't pick up.
When I come to find you. you're at a rave?
And you're asking what my problem is?
[man] We're gonna call the police!
Oh yeah? You wanna call the police?
I've got good news for you.
I am the fuckin' police!
You made your point. can we go?
Everyone gets it!
- Out.
- You put me in deep shit now. Thanks.
I put you in deep shit?
I miss 15 calls from you. that's my fault?
- What the hell was that about?
- I have no idea what happened.
I must've pocket dialed you.
Fine. They were pocket dials.
I come and find you at a rave
where everyone's high and wasted.
Taking MDMA. coke.
speed and who knows what else.
- For fuck's sake. Manon. you're 16.
- Do you think I took any of that?
- I hope not.
- I didn't.
I just came to hang out with my friends.
Without telling us?
- Who would I tell?
- I don't know. maybe your Mum and Dad?
Mom's out for dinner with her friends
and you're never around!
You think I haven't done this before?
I don't know.
Maybe if you were around more. you would.
Come on. Let's go.
You pulled a Bruce Lee. apparently.
You'd have done so much worse
if you'd been in my shoes.
Hm.
- This is great.
- Not bad. huh?
- Yeah.
- It's a company gift.
For the new job.
I wanted to tell you that. um…
I wanted to tell you
how much I admire you.
Always have.
You deserve… everything you've worked for.
And Manon's so talented.
She deserves better teachers
than what she can get here.
But. um…
If I'm being completely honest. I…
[gentle music playing]
I want you to stay.
[sighs]
Is there anything I can do
to convince you?
I don't know.
[indistinct radio chatter]
- No. they said it was quiet yesterday.
- That’s good.
[both grunting]
Right. Send it back right away.
[grunting]
Keep your guard up.
Even when you're striking.
[tense music playing]
[door opens]
- My report on the Kröller mission.
- Stick around.
What're you working on?
Hey.
You're trying to identify some ammo?
[turns pages]
Okay.
- Need some help?
- No.
You know I was at
weapon control before joining?
No. Guess you don't.
You know. even geniuses like you
could use help sometimes.
12-7 NATO.
[pensive music playing]
But it's not standard issue.
Where'd you get it?
I bet it's not
in the manufacturer's database.
And the serial number can't be traced.
Otherwise. it would've been.
You're wasting my time. Max. We done here?
This is specialized ammo
made by the military.
How could you possibly know that?
The army stopped making
their ammo a decade ago.
They only produced a small quantity
of these for research in weapons labs.
Wait. weapons labs?
Yeah. They took them out of circulation.
That's why it can't be traced.
You're sure?
Mm-hmm.
- Where you going?
- To see Christophe.
[Max] I'll come with.
[indistinct chatter]
Yes. that's good.
Yeah. very good.
Why'd they bring me that?
Excuse me. guys.
I didn't ask for a respirator.
- [nurse] Can I help you?
- We're here to visit our friend.
[nurse] Of course. go ahead.
[doctor] Hey. I'm talking to you!
Excuse me?
Come on. seriously?
Hey!
- It's one thing after another here.
- [David] What's going on?
[doctor] I didn't ask for a respirator.
- Excuse me.
- [nurse] Yes. Doctor?
I need to know
who's in charge of equipment.
I didn't order that.
[dramatic music playing]
[David] Holy shit.
We have to evacuate right now.
There's a bomb!
I'll take care of it.
Go do it right now. Go.
Okay. Get Tanya on the phone. now!
[suspenseful music playing]
Are you cold? You want your scarf?
No.
[cell phone ringing]
- Hello?
- [Max] Tanya?
It's Max. I'm at the hospital with David.
Christophe's room
was rigged with explosives.
- Have you evacuated the building?
- [Max] It's in progress.
- Can I video call you?
- No.
No. absolutely not.
Just put me on speaker and move
the phone away to avoid interference.
Okay.
- [Tanya] Can you hear me?
- [Max] Yeah. I hear you!
Tell me what you're seeing.
There's. uh… There's six tubes of CL-20.
There's wires connected inside the cart.
And it's. uh…
It's in a cart like in the O.R.
The first thing is.
make sure the cart won't trip anything.
Look everywhere. Around it. underneath it.
- [gunshots]
- [staff screaming]
[gunshot]
[Tanya] Anything. Max?
- Max?
- [Max] No. we're good.
- [Tanya] Follow the cable harness.
- [Max] Okay.
[David] We're evacuating the hospital!
Everyone out. now!
Excuse me. sir?
We have to get you out of here.
- [nurse] We need you in pediatrics!
- [doctor] Yeah. I'm coming. Coming!
Find me the chart-- Oh!
[alarm blaring]
There's. um… There's a plate
that's blocking me from getting in.
I have to open it.
No. no. no. Leave the plate.
You check that the plate
has no wires coming off of it first.
- [alarm blaring]
- You okay?
[suspenseful music continues]
[Tanya] So then you're going
to remove it very gently. okay?
- Don't take any chances.
- Just a minute. Okay.
- You still with me?
- Yeah. I hear you. Yeah.
[distant gunshots]
[people screaming]
- [indistinct yelling]
- [woman] Help!
[suspenseful music continues]
All right.
Okay. I got it open.
[Tanya] What do you see?
[Max] There's 12 more tubes of CL-20.
a detonator and a timer.
[Tanya] How much time left?
Three minutes. 30.
[Tanya] Find the live wire and cut it.
Okay.
I can't see a thing.
Max. do you read me?
Max. come in!
Okay.
Police! You seen anyone?
[man] There's a man in scrubs.
He's got a gun!
- Where is he?
- I don't know where he went.
He was shooting!
I need you to move.
[suspenseful music continues]
I'm with the police. I need you to move!
Freeze!
Put your weapon on the ground!
Do it slowly.
Hands above your head!
[car tires screeching]
[gunshots]
[intense music playing]
Max! What's your status?
[screeching]
[gunshots]
[gunfire]
[suspenseful music playing]
- [Tanya] You still with me?
- Yeah.
- Pretty sure I got it.
- How are you gonna cut it?
Uh…
[Tanya] And make sure
there's only one wire
connecting the detonator to the CL-20.
- [gunshots]
- Let's get outta here!
[tires screeching]
[intense music playing]
- We've got a problem.
- [Tanya] What?
There's a wire connected
to a second trigger.
Can you access that one?
[suspenseful music playing]
It's on the other side.
Can you cut both wires at the same time?
Oh. fuck.
[intense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[tires screech]
[gunshot]
[Tanya] Max. you there?
[sighs]
[Max] No. I can't. Dammit.
I can't cut both at the same time.
- Max!
- [Tanya] Just get out of there. now!
You still have time! Move!
[breathing heavily]
- [David] Max!
- I'm not leaving. I can't.
If you can hear me. don't take any risks!
I'm coming!
[Tanya] Max. Get out of there!
[Max] I can do this.
[suspenseful music playing]
Tell me what you need.
[Max] Grab the scissors.
You can't see me.
so you'll have to listen.
Yeah.
There's two detonators.
One on your side and one on mine.
We're gonna have
to cut them at the same time.
- Okay.
- There are two wires.
The one you want is on the right.
- Your right or my right?
- Your right.
Okay.
[suspenseful music continues]
Shit.
- How much time?
- 40 seconds.
[David] Fuck.
- I can't-- I can't see anything.
- It'll be fine. I can guide you.
Bring the scissors closer to me slowly.
And a little bit more to the right.
Good. Forward.
Forward just a bit more.
[music intensifies]
Yeah. there. That's it.
Stop moving. Don't move.
We cut on three.
Okay?
One. Two. Three.
- [David exhales]
- [music calms]
[tools clatter]
[exhales]
[panting]
You okay. honey? Yeah. you're okay.
[Tanya sighs]
Son of a bitch.
I'll go tell the others.
[coughs]
[exhales]
[chuckles]
I guess we live to fight another day.
[sighs]
[coughs]
You remember the lab where Laurent died?
[solemn music playing]
I think the guy who planted the bomb
is the guy you dragged outside.
So it's revenge.
That's what I think.
It's my fault.
[David] No. It was a mistake.
We all made mistakes that day.
[groans]
David. you can't outrun the past.
Just look.
[chuckles]
Look at me now.
You have--
[monitor beeping rapidly]
[monitor flatlines]
[unsettling music playing]
[music intensifies]
[somber music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
[music ends]
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-